=Betrayed Love=
= الحب المغدور =
=Episode 7=
= الحلقة 7 =
(Gangwu Xincun)
(جانجو شينكون)
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
I have poor reception here. I will go to another place.
لدي استقبال ضعيف هنا.  سأذهب إلى مكان آخر.
You can speak now.
يمكنك التحدث الآن.
Who?
من؟
Thank you for your cooperation, Mr. Shen.
شكرا لتعاونك ، السيد شين.
That's the waiter.
هذا هو النادل.
Who was in charge of the drinks party that night?
من كان المسؤول عن حفل المشروبات في تلك الليلة؟
It's me.
هذا أنا.
Dear, I'm hungry.
عزيزتي ، أنا جائع.
I'll go home and have a look.
سأذهب إلى المنزل وألقي نظرة.
Darling, I'm on my way.
حبيبي ، أنا في طريقي.
(Early next morning)
(في وقت مبكر من صباح اليوم التالي)
Here you go.
ها أنت ذا.
Your favorite basil sauce.
صوص الريحان المفضل لديك.
What is wrong?
ما المشكله؟
We haven't had breakfast like this for a long time.
لم نتناول الإفطار مثل هذا لفترة طويلة.
Let's eat slowly today.
دعونا نأكل ببطء اليوم.
There is soup in the pot.
يوجد حساء في القدر.
But we need to wait for a while.
لكن علينا الانتظار لبعض الوقت.
(Xu Jing; His name is Yang Zhe. No. 23, Ningzhou Lane, Yanhai Road)
(Xu Jing ؛ اسمه Yang Zhe. رقم 23 ، Ningbo Lane ، Yanhai Road)
I forgot I had made an appointment with a client.
لقد نسيت أنني قد حددت موعدًا مع أحد العملاء.
What client is more important than me?
أي عميل أكثر أهمية مني؟
I am for the good of the company.
أنا من أجل مصلحة الشركة.
(Yang Zhe)
(يانغ زهي)
Forget it. Work is important. Just go.
انسى ذلك.  العمل مهم.  فقط اذهب.
OK. Bye, darling.
نعم.  وداعا حبيبي.
Did you find it?
هل وجدتها؟
Yes, I did.
نعم فعلت.
But the neighbor said the man had just left.
لكن الجار قال إن الرجل غادر لتوه.
Xin.
شين.
Where the hell have you been these days?
أين كنت بحق الجحيم هذه الأيام؟
Why can't you listen to me?
لماذا لا تسمعني؟
Shen Zhuo is not as simple as you think.
Shen Zhuo ليس بهذه البساطة كما تعتقد.
He's right in front of my house now.
إنه أمام منزلي الآن.
I want to help you.
اريد مساعدتك.
Just stay out of this.
فقط ابق خارج هذا.
I don't need your help.
لست بحاجة لمساعدتكم.
I created a new account.
لقد قمت بإنشاء حساب جديد.
His e-money is in the account.
نقوده الإلكترونية في الحساب.
Where did you get it?
من اين حصلت عليه؟
Yang Zhe, are you crazy?
يانغ زهي ، هل أنت مجنون؟
You're committing a crime!
أنت ترتكب جريمة!
If it is not reasonable and legal,
إذا كان غير معقول وقانوني ،
everything you do will be futile!
كل ما تفعله سيكون بلا جدوى!
If you are unhappy,
إذا كنت غير سعيد ،
everything I do will be futile.
كل ما أفعله سيكون بلا جدوى.
Dear, we haven't had breakfast together for a long time.
عزيزي ، لم نتناول الإفطار معًا منذ فترة طويلة.
I made you your favorite sunny-side up. Taste it.
لقد جعلت لك الجانب المشمس المفضل لديك.  تذوقه.
I want to try something different these days.
أريد أن أجرب شيئًا مختلفًا هذه الأيام.
(Xu Jing: Time is opportunity.)
(شو جينغ: الوقت فرصة.)
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Happy birthday!
عيد مولد سعيد!
Guess what gift I'll give you.
احزر ما هي الهدية التي سأقدمها لك.
Will you give me a good husband?
هل ستعطيني زوجًا صالحًا؟
Just wait for the express package.
فقط انتظر الحزمة السريعة.
I put a bug in your gift to Xu Jing.
لقد وضعت خطأ في هديتك لـ Xu Jing.
I'll transfer the content to you.
سأقوم بنقل المحتوى إليك.
(You are so naughty.)
(أنت شقي جدا.)
(Today is my birthday.)
(اليوم عيد ميلادي.)
This dose is enough to kill her.
هذه الجرعة تكفي لقتلها.
Guan Xin, calm down!
غوان شين ، اهدأ!
Why did you save me?
لماذا أنقذتني؟
I don't want you to die.
لا أريدك أن تموت.
Have a good rest in the coming days.
احصل على راحة جيدة في الأيام القادمة.
(I believe she will definitely come back.)
(أعتقد أنها ستعود بالتأكيد.)
(It's just a matter of time.)
(أنها فقط مسألة وقت.)
("New Leader" of Guan Group Company, Shen Zhuo, is to take office)
(سيتولى "القائد الجديد" لشركة Guan Group ، Shen Zhuo ، منصبه)
He is going to take charge of Guan Group Company now.
سوف يتولى مسؤولية شركة Guan Group الآن.
It's time I went back.
حان وقت عودتي.